





Last Active: 23-Jan-21 Last Modified: 23-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Currently working as Software Engineer at EPSON with corporate experience 2.4 yrs. Having good understanding in C and OOPS features in C++. Good understanding in fundamentals of socket programming. Good communication skills along with problem solving skills. Able to learn new concepts and technologies quickly, with "CAN DO" nature.

Work Experience

Epson as Associate Software Engineer May 2019 to Till Date

Requirement Gathering, Design, Development of small to medium scale software for Dot Matrix and Thermal Line Printers using C, C++ and C# technology.

- Nash Industries Pvt. Ltd. as Software Developer Jun 2018 to Apr 2019
- Vector India Pvt. Ltd as Trainee Embedded Engineer Mar 2017 to Sep 2017

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (not specified) from Ganpat university in 2016 PG: CS (CS) from Ganpat university, ahmedabad in 2016

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
C,C++	
Python	
C#	

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Windows,Linux	
Visual Studio, PAGE, PyCharm	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Gujarati	Proficient	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.